neworleansonline.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy

##### Last Updated on October 18, 2017

NewOrleans.com has created this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain our personal information collection practices and your options regarding such data. The Privacy Policy applies to your access and use of the NewOrleans.com Websites (as defined in our Terms of Use), mobile applications and other online programs ("Online Services"). By using or downloading any of our Online Services, you are agreeing that you have read and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with any part of this Privacy Policy, please do not use any of our Online Services.

NewOrleans.com controls and operates its business and Online Services from within the United States of America. Our online privacy practices are governed by the laws of the United States and the State of Louisiana, which may differ from privacy laws in your state or home country. By submitting your personal information to us through the use of our Online Services, you consent to the transfer of your personal information to any country and its use and disclosure in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable U.S. federal and state laws.

We may change our Privacy Policy, so please check this page from time to time, as your continued use of the Online Services after we publish our changes, indicates your acceptance of any changed terms. You can tell when the Privacy Policy was last updated by reviewing the "Last Updated" date at the top of the page.

You can jump to specific areas of our Privacy Policy by clicking on the links below, or you can read on for the full Privacy Policy:

## Information We Collect

Whether you access our Online Services from your computer, smart phone, tablet or other mobile device, NewOrleans.com and its agents may collect some information that identifies you or relates to you as an individual ("Personal Information"), such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address, user name and password (for account administration), device ID, including IP address, geolocation (if using a mobile application and you consent to providing it), and additional personal information necessary for the administration of certain promotional events.

In addition, we may collect other types of data ("Other Information") that do not reveal your identity or that do not relate directly to you or any other individual, such as Web browser and device information, including operating system, demographic information and other information provided by you that we may combine with other users of our Online Services or use on its own, mobile application usage data, aggregated information such as "click stream" information such as entry and exit points for our Online Services (including referring URLs or domains), certain Online Services traffic statistics, page views, and impressions, and information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies described in more detail later in this Privacy Policy. In addition, when users request pages on our Online Services, our servers automatically log the IP address of the particular user. The IP address is a unique number assigned to your computer in order to identify it whenever you are surfing the web.

## How We Use Personal Information We Collect

We may use Personal Information about you for purposes described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed to you through our Online Services. For example, we may use Personal Information:

  * to process and manage your requests for products and services, including newsletters, guidebooks, and other items
  * respond to and/or fulfill your inquiries or requests, and to post your comments, ratings or statements on message boards or in our online discussion areas or forums
  * create and deliver personalized promotions, including by combining your Personal Information with Other Information, such as the amounts and types of bookings or itineraries you make and discounts or benefits you use
  * communicate with you by mail, telephone, facsimile, e-mail, mobile alerts and SMS text messaging about New Orleans or our affiliates, including communications about your itineraries or purchases, your services, accounts, sweepstakes or contests you enter, your requests for information or other items, and to update you about changes to our Online Services
  * communicate with you, including by mail, telephone, facsimile, e-mail, mobile alerts and SMS text messaging, in connection with our marketing efforts, including sending you offers and promotions that you can take advantage of through our Online Services or at relevant physical venues around or near New Orleans and offer personalized collection, filtering, and delivery of information, including serving advertisements while you are visiting New Orleans.
  * allow you to send communications or gifts (including through our mobile application) to friends or family through our Online Services (conditioned on your representation to us that you are permitted to use and provide us with the recipient's name and e-mail address;
  * further our business or operational purposes, for example, data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention; and
  * enhance, improve or modify our Online Services, to identify usage trends, determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and advertisements and to operate and expand our business activities.

NewOrleans.com may send you "transactional or relationship" communications using various electronic communication, including email and mobile communications. "Transactional or relationship" communications may include, for example, notices to facilitate a recent transaction you have conducted or messages with information about your existing account. If, at any time, you decide you would rather not receive these types of communications from NewOrleans.com, you can opt out by following the "opt-out" or "unsubscribe" or "STOP" instructions in the relevant communication or update the contact preferences for your NewOrleans.com account.

Please note: You must opt in (i.e., expressly consent) to receive text messages (SMS) from NewOrleans.com. Any such opt-in will be subject to this Privacy Policy and NewOrleans.com will only send you SMS text messages if you opt in to receive them from us.

## How We May Disclose Personal Information We Collect

Your privacy is very important to us. We generally won't disclose your Personal Information to anyone outside of NewOrleans.com, except in the following circumstances:

### Service Providers

We may disclose your Personal Information to third-party service providers to provide us with services such as website hosting, professional services, including information technology services and related infrastructure, customer service, e-mail delivery, auditing and other similar services.

### To Perform Services You Request

We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties in order to perform services you request, such as fulfillment of newsletter or guidebook requests, or functions you initiate, such as when you post information and materials on message boards and social media forums, including via Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, etc. Please note that when you post information in a public forum, it becomes public information.

In addition, we may disclose your Personal Information in order to identify you to anyone to whom you send communications or gifts through our Online Services.

### Corporate Changes

We may disclose your information to a third party in connection with a corporate reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock, including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings.

### Other Legal Reasons

In addition, we may use or disclose your Personal Information as we deem necessary or appropriate:

  * under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence;
  * to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence;
  * to comply with subpoenas and other legal processes;
  * to pursue available remedies or limit damages we may sustain;
  * to protect our operations or those of any of our Affiliates;
  * to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of NewOrleans.com, you and others; and
  * to enforce our Terms of Use and any other terms and conditions.

## How We May Use and Disclose Other Information We Collect

Similarly, we generally use Other Information for any purpose not prohibited by law. In particular, we may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, sell, or otherwise disclose or use any and all Other Information, provided that such information does not personally identify you. Other Information that we collect generally will not personally identify you or be correlated to you individually for external purposes.

Where we combine Other Information with Personal Information in a way that can identify you or be used to identify you personally, we will treat that information as Personal Information, subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

## Your Options

To manage and correct any factual inaccuracies in the information we have on file about you, please follow the directions in the e-mail or other relevant electronic communication you receive from us.

## How We Protect Your Personal Information

NewOrleans.com has implemented reasonable safeguards designed to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of Personal Information provided or collected through our Online Services.

Unfortunately, no system or online transmission of data can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and you should always take appropriate security measures to protect your Personal Information, including ensuring that you have up-to-date antivirus software. If you believe that your NewOrleans.com account or any information you provided to us is no longer secure, please notify us immediately using the Contact Us information provided below.

## Cookies

"Cookies" are small text files containing pieces of data that are placed in your computer's Web browser to store your preferences. Cookies are not themselves personally identifiable, but may be linked to Personal Information that you provide to us through your interaction with our Online Services. A Cookie will typically contain the name of the domain (Internet location) from which the Cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the Cookie (its expiration period), and a value (such as a randomly generated unique number).

### How We Use Cookies

NewOrleans.com and its agents use Cookies so that we can improve your online experience; for example, by remembering you when you come back to visit the Websites, and making the content you see more relevant to you. Cookies also enable us to track online purchases made through our Online Services.

### Your Options for Cookies

Web browsers allow some control of most Cookies. Please consult your particular Web browser's settings. You can learn more about Cookies, see what Cookies have been set on your computing device and learn how to manage and delete them at [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

### Online Advertising

NewOrleans.com also uses Cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags, web beacons and clear GIF files, to help manage our online advertising program. These technologies are provided by our advertising management partners and enable them to recognize a unique Cookie that has been placed on your Web browser, which in turn enables us and these advertising management partners to learn which advertisements bring users to our Online Services.

NewOrleans.com and our advertising management partners also may use these technologies to track the actions of users of our Online Services, to measure statistics of our marketing efforts, and to deliver advertisements on our Online Services that may be more relevant to individual consumers and to otherwise improve the experience of consumers using our Online Services.

## Social Networking and Third Party Sites

When you link to our Online Services through any social networking or third party websites, applications or services ("Third Party Services"), please remember that you are also bound by the privacy policies of such Third Party Services, and NewOrleans.com does not control and therefore is not responsible for the privacy practices of such Third Party Services. You should consult the privacy policies of such Third Party Services to understand their information practices.

## Your California Privacy Rights

If you live in California and have an established business relationship with us, you can request a list of the personal information we have shared with third parties for their marketing purposes. We will also give you a list of the third parties that have received your information. You can make a request one time each year. To exercise your rights, you can contact us by email at [online@neworleans.com](mailto:online@neworleans.com) or as set forth in the Contact Us section below. Please be sure to mention when you contact us that you are making a "California Shine the Light" inquiry. We will respond within 30 days.

## Children's Online Privacy

NewOrleans.com does not target children and does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). When a user discloses personal information on our Online Services, the user is representing to us that he or she is at least thirteen (13) years of age.

If you are the parent or guardian of a child under the age of thirteen (13), who you believe has provided NewOrleans.com with personally identifiable information through our Online Services, please e-mail us at [online@neworleans.com](mailto:online@neworleans.com) so that we can delete the child's information from our records.

## International

This English-language Privacy Policy is NewOrleans.com's official statement of our privacy practices. In case of any inconsistency between this English-language Privacy Policy and its translation into any other language, this English-language document will take precedence over such translation.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding our NewOrleans.com's privacy practices, please do not hesitate to contact us as follows:

E-mail: [online@neworleans.com](mailto:online@neworleans.com)  
Telephone: (504) 566-5011  
U.S. Mail: 2020 St. Charles Ave., New Orleans 70130
